<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Secnettool</title>
    <link>https://81app.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Secnettool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 23:59:15 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://81app.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Yings for macOS</title>
      <link>https://81app.github.io/post/macos-yings-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 23:59:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://81app.github.io/post/macos-yings-help/</guid>
      <description>Overview Yings is a proxy utility which used shadowsocks, shadowsocks is a secure socks5 proxy, designed to protect your internet traffic.
Features  Super Fast and secured with industry level encryption algorithm. Suports auto mode and global mode With eight built-in proxy servers, more proxy servers will be available soon. No registration and login, easy to use.  The difference of Auto Mode and Global Mode Auto Mode: You know some websites is blocked in some country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy of Yings</title>
      <link>https://81app.github.io/post/yings-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:52:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://81app.github.io/post/yings-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Yings is a proxy utility which used shadowsocks, shadowsocks is a secure socks5 proxy, designed to protect your internet traffic.
Data Collection Yings is just a proxy tool that provides network acceleration. We will not collect any of your information.
In order to improve product quality, we provide email feedback function, if you have any suggestions, you can send us an email. This email content is only used to help us communicate and improve product quality, we will not use it anywhere else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Secnettool for macOS</title>
      <link>https://81app.github.io/post/macos-secnettool-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 18:40:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://81app.github.io/post/macos-secnettool-intro/</guid>
      <description>What is VPN? A VPN, or virtual private network, is a secure tunnel between two or more devices. VPNs are used to protect private web traffic from snooping, interference, and censorship.
What is Secnettool? Secnettool is an IPsec VPN App, which encrypts your network traffic, so that nobody between you and the VPN server can eavesdrop on your data as it travels via the Internet. This is especially useful when using unsecured networks, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Secnettool for iOS</title>
      <link>https://81app.github.io/post/secnettool-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:15:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://81app.github.io/post/secnettool-introduction/</guid>
      <description>What is VPN? A VPN, or virtual private network, is a secure tunnel between two or more devices. VPNs are used to protect private web traffic from snooping, interference, and censorship.
What is Secnettool? Secnettool is an IPsec VPN App, which encrypts your network traffic, so that nobody between you and the VPN server can eavesdrop on your data as it travels via the Internet. This is especially useful when using unsecured networks, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy of Secnettool</title>
      <link>https://81app.github.io/post/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:04:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://81app.github.io/post/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>The Privacy Policy Secnettool keeps no logs which enable interference with your IP address, the moment or content of your data traffic. We make express reference to the fact that we do not record in logs communication contents or data regarding the accessed websites or the IP addresses .
Install &amp;amp; Updates We have the right to install certificates and future updates at any time without any notice.
Changes We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://81app.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 23:12:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://81app.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Overview Secnettool is an IPsec VPN Client, which encrypts your network traffic, so that nobody between you and the VPN server can eavesdrop on your data as it travels via the Internet. This is especially useful when using unsecured networks, e.g. at coffee shops, airports or hotel rooms.
Contact Email: secnettool@gmail.com
Twitter: https://twitter.com/secnettool</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>